Cen
finally got around to trying out the
Cen Rider Dikit Legend Edition.
Honestly, I'm waiting for the price to drop before
buying.  The manual book is
really thick, guys.  And this card is also
very good.  The assembly process is easy and there
are no problems at all.  And this is what the
figure looks like, guys.  And the
details are really detailed.   The
farming aura is
really visible, guys.  And this one doesn't
have any stickers at all like the other brands,
guys.  Wow, the details on these eyes are
really cool, guys.  The fighting part is no
less detailed and has gimmicks like this,
guys.  In the booker section, there is also a
small detail of the rider logo.  Overall, the
details are really great, guys.  For
accessories, we get additional
hand options and the details are also no
joke, Guys.  Then there are
small cards like this.  There are
additional parts to change the ride booker
into a sword or shooting mode
like this.  Lastly we get the stain
base.  In terms of articulation, this is also
really great, guys.  I've
also used butterfly join.  So it's really fun
to pose in cool poses like
this, guys.   The
figure's height is 19 cm and
this is the comparison with the Galaxy
Version and this is the comparison with the
regular SHF.  Well, that's a brief review
of the blockis comen Rider DKE.
Anyway, if the price isn't too high,
this is really worth it, guys.